SO I UP LOADED A
VIDEO SHOW CASING MY POLISHED
PLANETS CAUSE I ALSO ADDED
FIVE OTHER PLANETS IN TWENTY
TWELVE AND ALTHOUGH IT WENT
UNDER THE RADAR FOR QUITE
A FEW YEARS YEAH EVENTUALLY
IT BECAME MY MOST VIEWED
VIDEO BUT WHY AM I
RETURNING TO THIS TOPIC EIGHT
YEARS LATER WELL BACK THEN
I DIDN'T REALLY WANT OR
KNOW HOW TO SHARE MY
WORLD FILES ONLINE SO I
THOUGHT THE VIDEO ALONE WAS
ENOUGH NOW WITH A NEW
PERSPECTIVE AND WANTING TO BE
MORE COLLABORATIVE IN THE YOU
TUBE ONLINE WORLD I'M COMING
TO THE REALIZATION THAT IT
WOULD BE REALLY COOL TO
SEE OTHER MINE CRAFT PLAYERS
PLAYING AROUND WITH MY GIANT
EARTH IN THEIR OWN CREATIVE
WAYS SO I'LL PUT LINKS
TO DOWNLOAD ALL THE WORLD
FILES IN THE DESCRIPTION SO
YOU GUYS CAN PLAY WITH
IT REMEMBER IT'S GOT FOUR
TIMES THE BLOCKS SIX TIMES
THE PLANETS AND A HUNDRED
TIMES THE CARING ES THAN
THAT OTHER WORLD AND UH
I I KNOW THAT PEP
IN F T ASSES ONE
TO ONE EARTH REPLICA WILL
BLOW
THE WATER WHEN IT'S DONE
BUT THEY'RE NOT QUITE DONE
YET I'LL ALSO PUT THE
YO SAM ITTY AND MEN
JUROR SPONGE WORLD FILES ONLINE
BUT NOT THE POCK WILL
BELLS CANNON IN MINE CRAFT
OR SLOPE DESERT WORLDS SINCE
THOSE RELY ON MOD THAT
ARE DEFUNCT NOW I ALSO
WANT TO SAY THANKS TO
MOE HANG AND NOTCH FOR
MAKING WORLD FILES BACKWARD COMPATIBLE
BECAUSE I WAS WORRIED FOR
THE LONGEST TIME THAT MY
WORLD FILES FROM MINE CRAFT
ONE POINT TWO WOULD BE
SUPER DIFFICULT TO CONVERT INTO
THE MODERN MINE CRAFT ONE
POINT SIXTEEN BUT IN TRUTH
IT COULDN'T HAVE BEEN EASIER
BACK THE TOPIC OF THE
PLANETS WORLD IN THE LAST
WEEK I'VE ALSO MANUALLY ADDED
MAYBE FIFTEEN TO TWENTY NEW
OBJECTS TO THE SIZE COMPARISON
ARENA SINCE I AM THE
SCALE OF THE UNIVERSE GUY
I GUESS SO I THOUGHT
IT MIGHT BE FUN TO
USE THIS VIDEO TO SHOW
THEM OFF TO YOU SO
LET'S JUMP BACK IN TO
MINE CRAFT